What does it mean for two sets to be disjoint?

Two sets are disjoint if none of the elements that exist in either set exist in both sets. 
Ex. A:{1,2,3} and B:{4,5,6} are disjoint, while A:{1,2,3} and B:{3,4,5} are not (3 is an element of both A and B).

What is the union of two sets?

The union of two sets is the set containing all of the elements that exist in either set.
Ex. A:{1,2,3,4} and B:{3,4,5,6}, therfore A∪B:{1,2,3,4,5,6}.